[music]
in the pocket on third and long. ROSS
SACKED BY CHRIS JONES. Stone cold caught
by Kelsey inside the 10. Inside the
five. KELSEY LEAPS. TOUCHDOWN. DARE AT
THE 10. ANGLING to the five INTO THE END
ZONE. LEFT SIDE AND IT is good.
[screaming]
Good. Here comes a rush and he's GOING
TO GO DOWN. GEORGE CARLUS. [music]
[music] WELL, merry Christmas everyone.
Mitchus with you along with senior team
reporter Matt McMullen. I'm not into
moral victories. I'm not into losing,
but the feeling of this game, a 20-13
loss to the Broncos, very different than
I felt since the Colts game because
there was some incredible effort
tonight. The Chiefs had a chance to get
an improbable victory with a patchwork
lineup. And the effort tonight, I
thought was incredible.
>> Yeah. So, on one end, sure. This was our
fifth loss in a row and our eighth
one-score loss this year. But on the
other side, you're totally right. Our
guys fought tonight and I'm proud of how
they fought tonight. And you know, a
couple weeks ago, we talked about, hey,
we're not going to make the playoffs
this year, but this time can be used for
player development. And we didn't really
see it last week, which was
disappointing. We saw it in spades here
tonight. I mean, Bashard Smith made
plays, null Williams made plays. We'll
talk about it over the course of the
show, but um you know, we lost tonight,
but our guys, they played with heart,
and we saw the player development we
were hoping to see over the last couple
weeks, and I'm excited right now about
2026 based on tonight.
>> The Denver Broncos came into the game
number one in the league in sacks. They
were actually trending to maybe set an
all-time sack record. They had one
tonight. Nick Bonito had zero. Jonathan
Cooper had zero. Chris Olen part of
that. And an offensive line, and I'm
going to give Creed Humphrey and Trey
Smith credit. we did on the podcast.
That offensive line came to play and
they took the fight to the Denver front.
>> Yeah, they did. Uh that Broncos defense
is impressive. Uh they have 13 more
sacks than the next closest team in the
NFL. I mean, they've been having high
sack totals in just about every game
this year. And for the Chiefs offense to
go out there with their third string
tackles on both sides. I mean, think
about it. Essip and Chu Godri neither
played high school football and they're
facing this defensive front and they
were great. really throughout this game
and gave our offense a chance. And
again, that's the player development
aspect because we talked on field pass
about how okay, yeah, our tackles didn't
play great last week. Well, how do they
respond now a week later? I think they
bounced back in a huge way here tonight
facing a really tough challenge in
Denver and they were great throughout
this game and they gave us a chance.
Great thing to see.
>> Special teams Bashard Smith a 45 yd
return. No special teams penalties
tonight. Chiefs came in last in average
field position um in the NFL. Tonight
they were outstanding and again gave the
Chiefs a chance to win, but special
teams tonight was different effort,
execution, and being more pristine.
>> Yeah, just great across the board on
special teams. And talking about
Brashard, that punt return was great.
How about his touchdown though? Who'
that remind you of on that touchdown?
That was Jerick McKinnon right there.
>> And we talked about that early in the
year that Bashard can maybe be a Jerick
McKinnon kind of player. has to grow
into that, right? Well, haven't seen
Bashard a ton this year, but when he had
chances here in this game tonight, he
made some plays and on that touchdown
reminded me of Jerick McKinnon. Looking
forward to seeing more of that next
season.
>> And Chris Oloken, this is going to be a
big week for him next week against the
Raiders because now all of a sudden you
have a serious discussion about maybe
Chris Olen can be the guy that gets you
through the offseason or bridges the gap
to when Patrick Mahomes returns.
>> He had some Patrick Mahomes impressions
here tonight. uh he had the ball that he
fumbled, picked it up, still found Guju
down the field and on the drive that
ended up with the game tying field goal,
I believe, uh was scrambling all over
the place just like Patrick would and
found I think Juju once again down the
field. Uh Chris has something and I'm
proud of him because he's waited a long
time for that moment to go out there,
run out of the tunnel as a starter on
NFL field in a regular season game. He
held his own. He had us in this game
against one of the best defenses in
football. Let's see what he has next
week. But great start for Chris here
tonight.
>> We're going to talk about the defense
here, but let's go to the podium now and
get reaction.
[snorts]
>> All right. Um, everybody came through
okay um, healthwise.
Um, first of all, merry Christmas to you
guys and um, to the fans. Uh, thank you
for uh, coming out there and supporting
us. Uh the guys felt that their effort
was phenomenal tonight. We got to play a
lot of young guys which is a positive
and you know they're following what the
veterans are all about and their culture
that they've established here. So um
it's um that that's a positive that we
could take out of this thing. Uh proud
of Chris for going out and jumping in a
quarterback on a short week and handling
what he what he needed to handle there.
Um, I I thought he did a did a good job
of running things and and executing when
needed.
Uh, and then Kel had a had a nice day.
Finished strong there with a few
catches. And then defensively,
uh, I thought we did a nice job. Bolton
was on fire tonight and,
uh, Connor and Chris had another sack,
you know, in there.
Um, and then special teams, we, you
know, we we did some good things there.
Returns with Smith. I thought, uh,
Smitty did a nice job of with a couple
nice returns, and that's something
positive that you can you can take into
the future there with him. So, um, and
that's knowing that the season's not
over yet. So, we we understand that.
But, uh, all in all, we want to win the
football game. Number one, you want to
win the football game, and I I really
don't care who's in. That's uh that's
the primary goal. And so, uh, we came up
short, uh, uh, but again, gave a good
effort there, um, in doing that. So,
with that, time's yours.
>> Andy, you're running the game and you're
emotional about that, but I do wonder if
you had any moments during the game or
after where you honored whether it was
going to be Travis's last home game.
>> No, but it was great to see him get a
couple of those catches. Those were big
big catches. And uh we'll we'll talk
another time about all of that and um
you know you guys are going to have an
opportunity to talk to him here in a
minute. So
>> Andy, you mentioned how much you feel he
kind of set the tone for what the
defense did.
>> Yeah. So when I say the young guys
follow uh the veteran guys, he's one of
those veteran guys. And so you you know
all of a sudden you see Williams getting
sticking his nose in there as a corner
making big plays. Fulton made some nice
plays out there. So all these guys are
they follow these leaders and um uh you
know as coaches we give them the
direction and those guys lead by
example. So it's uh that's an important
thing to have on your team.
>> What kind of Chrisen and Pepp?
[clears throat]
Yeah, that was kind of a that was kind
of a neat deal, I guess, there, but I
hadn't thought about that. But yeah,
that was great. I I thought Smitty did a
nice job of of breaking the tackle
there. So, uh that wasn't an easy easy
play to make. Um
but he made the most of it and the you
could see the guys were happy for him.
He's a he's a good kid.
>> In terms of of Smith, what areas do you
see that you see [clears throat] that
can grow?
>> Sure.
>> Yeah. So, he hasn't played a ton of
running back, so all of this stuff is is
good for him. We're moving him all over
the place, so he can handle it mentally,
first of all, and and that's a that's a
plus the way we're using him. Um, the
second thing is he he catch the football
as [clears throat] well as run the
football, and uh that that helps you out
down the down the road. Um,
so I listen, he's he's been I won't say
a pleasant surprise, but he's done a
nice job. And then he'll get stronger as
he goes here. Physically stronger. These
guys, they always put on a little bit of
weight and strength uh after their first
year and that'll help his game going
forward there. And then the return
ability. So you got a chance to see
that.
>> Andy, what Christian F in terms of at
least playing time?
>> Yeah. So, I I thought he played like he
was healthy and so that uh um Brett
brought him in here knowing that he was
a good football player, but he he hadn't
been able to stay healthy. So, he was
able to get himself in a position now
where he's feeling better football-wise
and get himself out there and and play,
but that's what he's capable of doing,
you know.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Merry Christmas again.
comes near side. SMITH WITH THE CATCH,
ANGLING TO THE NEAR SIDE AND BREAKS A
TACKLE. TOUCHDOWN [screaming]
KANSAS CITY. IT'S BRASHIDE SMITH'S FIRST
NATIONAL LEAGUE NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE
TOUCHDOWN AND IT GIVES THE CHIEFS A 6-3
lead at 1249 to go. Second quarter.
NFL is a tough league. Sometimes you
wait and then in a blink of an eye you
are put in the center stage like a
Broadway play that you've waited four
years to be in. Chris Oloken with me
now. First of all, the effort and what
you've shown the last two games is
remarkable. Kind of walk us through
what's been going through your mind cuz
you got thrust right in the middle of
the action.
>> Yeah. Uh things are definitely happening
fast. That's for sure. you know, uh, you
play Sunday and then you go into a
Christmas game, short week, and, you
know, the coaches did a great job just
simplifying everything and making it
easy for me and the guys. I mean, I
can't say enough about their effort and,
you know, all them having my back, you
know, out there as well. So, um, it's
definitely not just a oneman show out
there. Everyone uh, pulled their weight
and, uh, I love I love this team, man.
>> Chris, this team, the Broncos lead the
league in sacks. Only one sack in this
game. What about guys rallying around
you and then you showing both in this
game and the Tennessee game, hey guys, I
can do this. Just help me out.
>> Well, when you have guys like Trey and
Creed and like Trav, they're telling
you, hey, we're behind you, [music] man.
Like, we got your back. You know, that
just gives me even more confidence and
um you know, I'm it's I've been blessed
to, you know, go to battle with those
guys and you know, we didn't get the
outcome we want today, but I'm super
proud of, you know, the way we fought
and you know, we're you know, one play
away from winning the game.
get your first touchdown pass of your
career out to Brashard. Walk us through
that play and what you were thinking.
>> So that was one of my favorite plays
down in the red zone all week and um I
was telling Bashard I was like I had a
feeling all week that we were both going
to get our first touch on the same play.
So I have Allan right in there trying to
figure out how we can split that thing
in half and make sure we [music] both
get a little piece of the pie. Um but
no, we we honestly we were expecting man
got a little zone look and they sort of
eyes just got sniffy and uh you know he
was wide open in the flat. He made a
great play. You know, Solomon would say,
"Cut the ball in half. You guys both get
a half ball." But super proud of you and
the way you fought. Uh, and your poise.
How much of that has come from the fact
that you have just prepared, prepared,
prepared now for 40 years?
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, like you said, four
years of preparation. Um, I feel like
when I'm out there, it's just almost
like practice. You know, I've taken so
many mental reps, you know, in the back
in the shadows when, you know, Pat's up
and guarding those guys. So, um, you
know, I I sort of say like when when the
lights are on, that's when I play my
best, man. I I'm out there playing free
and, uh, you know, when you have great
guys around you, too, Ryan, behind you,
um, just makes my job even easier.
>> I'm aware how close you and Pat are in
Tennessee. I felt like I could hear his
voice behind me. Calling this gig going,
"Come on, Chris. You can do this,
Chris." How much has Pat not only helped
you in the last two games, but how much
have you learned from him in these four
years?
>> I mean, invaluable the last four years.
I mean, I don't have an older brother,
but he's probably one of the closest
things I have to it. Um, along with a
couple friends back home, he's just been
so he's been so great with me in terms
of my development. I mean, I look back
and where I started my rookie year to
now. And, uh, he's helped my career on
and off the field so much. So, uh, I
could never repay him for, you know,
what he's done for my career up to this
point.
>> Go get another holiday gift, an Olken
jersey. Number 19, Chris Oloken. Yes.
Yes, sir.
Hi guys.
Look like you took bit of a moment in
the player introductions, Kelsey, to
just take a minute to look around. Just
wonder what what went through your head
and just what you wanted to appreciate
in that moment considering this could be
the last home game.
>> You know, it's uh you only get a few of
those where you just get to stand there
and appreciate 60 to 70,000 Chiefs fans
creating it for you. So, um I always
embrace that moment, man. It's fun. And
uh hopefully I got everybody fired up
for it.
>> Travis, any extra emotions to this game?
I mean,
>> yeah, it's a Christmas game, baby. It's
a whole lot of emotion, man. Have
everybody in the world watching you. Um
you get to go out there with a guy, a
young guy like Chris Oladukan. Um prime
time television. Excited for him,
excited for the guys around us. A lot of
young guys getting opportunities to, you
know, taste what this NFL life on a on a
big stage feels like. Um, and I just
wanted to get out there and get a win
for those guys. Man,
>> that's what I was asking. But of course,
secondarily, uh, you've been asked
enough by us and I know you asked by by
Tony yesterday about the possibility
home. Did that ever cross your mind
throughout the game?
>> No. The only time it ever crossed my
mind is I was driving in the other day
and I saw how much the Powerball was and
I was like, man, if I could just win
that,
I wouldn't have to work another day of
my life.
>> That's what's keeping you here?
>> Oh, no, man. Uh, honestly, I've been
just focused on trying to win football
games, man. I'll let that be a decision
that I make with my family, friends, the
Chiefs organization, um, when the time
comes.
>> Okay. With
given this is Chris's first start, I
know it's a lot different than what
happened Sunday in Nashville. Just how
do you think he handled this
responsibility? And did he sort of show
you something that maybe you would not
have known otherwise?
>> Yeah, man. That was the first time I've
ever seen someone try and draw the
defense to him by by fumbling it. That
was pretty. It was like a little yo-yo
trick he put on him, man. That was the
first time. No, I'm proud of him, man.
His uh throughout the week, his
attention to detail, his
professionalism, his leadership. Um
couldn't be happier for the guy. [music]
Obviously wish we could have got that
win for him on a on a big game against a
rival. But um I'm proud of him, man. I'm
proud of the way he uh he led us into
victory and and kept fighting, man.
>> What's the best part about playing,
>> man?
I would say the tradition. You can feel
it. You can feel the the kids and the
and you know the the generations of of
happiness and the generations of just
love that they have uh coming together
on Sundays and cheering for their team.
Man, it's a it's a beautiful thing, man.
And um and you know, it's uh it's
something I know I'll cherish forever is
uh is those moments coming out of the
tunnel or uh just making a big play for
him late in the game. Um, and uh, that's
why we love Arrowhead, man. It's a it's
a special and unique unique stadium,
especially when they started turning off
the lights for us on intros, man, and
making it more epic.
>> You you're a a hype man. You'll get your
teammates fired up. Uh, I saw Chris
whole team gather around him before the
game. What What was What was Chris Olado
making his first start trying to get you
guys hyped up before you had the locker
room?
>> That that we're here fighting for each
other. you know, I think he had the
right message um to be, you know, we're
a team. No matter what this record is,
we're out here fighting for each other.
You're going to wear the the Chief's
Arrow head on your helmet and come out
here in a red jersey in front of this
crowd, man. You're going to give it your
all. And um he was just making sure
everybody knew that that he was ready
for a dog fight and that uh um that he
was going to lead us in victory,
>> lead us into the game.
>> You set the standard here for pretty
much over a decade. How much do you
embrace leading these guys,
>> man? And it's uh it's something that I I
take as like second nature at this
point, man. I've I've followed big coach
Andy Reid, baby. And he's done it the
right way. He's done it with integrity.
He's done it with a lot of love and uh
and a lot of uh care for the people
around him, not only just players, but
coaches as well. you guys have seen is
his is uh his you know [music] just the
coaches underneath go other places have
success and he he tries to build
everybody to make everybody [music] the
best possible player coach or uh
whatever their position is in the
building and um I it's just second
nature to me at this point following his
lead u making sure that I'm doing
everything I can to keep everybody um
focused locked in having fun and uh and
and trying to win football games
Let's go, Sam. We'll go around the room
here. Go Sam. Travis, you described
Arrowhead. Do you remember the first
time you felt that you felt part of
that? Just what the way you described
it?
>> Um, it's been so long. Uh, I I mean, you
feel it the the first game you you go
to, you know, it's it's I remember going
to the games my rookie year, even when I
was in the suits with a knee brace on,
you know, you you feel the excitement.
Um, I think we won our first eight games
when we got here and it was by by the
time we got to like our fifth, sixth
game at home, man, it was rocking and
people were here loud and proud and um
it was just it was a beautiful thing,
man. So, uh, I would probably say my
rookie year, you really found how
special this place is.
>> Thank you, Travis. You've, uh, it's the
first game you played obviously here
without Patrick in a long time. We saw
him tonight [snorts] in the suite
himself with the deep brakes. Um, has he
tried to sort of encourage you about
next season, the possibility of you guys
playing again? Have there been any
conversations about based on how his
rehab goes, you might want to stick
around for one more season?
>> I haven't talked to him about that. I I
feel like he's going to be the the most
competitive guy possible in his rehab to
get back and hopefully get back by the
start of the season, but um obviously,
you know, franchise quarterback, you
want to be smart with everything like
that, but he's going to he's going to
compete his ass off
>> in the offseason and everything. So, I
think uh I haven't talked to him
>> about any of that, man. I'm just uh you
know I wish uh I wish obviously this
season wouldn't have happened the way it
did um with him going down and uh it was
uh yeah
>> you've never had a season like this with
Andy with you know being six and 10.
What did you learn about him as a coach
in a season like this that maybe you
didn't know before now?
I mean, you know, you you go through ups
and downs and seasons and you find
yourself in situations where you got to
you got to, you know, circle the wagons,
find dig yourself out of a hole. Um, and
I know Coach Reed from day one has
always been that guy that's going to
lead us uh through all of that and be
the be the main one that raises his hand
and says, "I need to be better for you."
You know, put the accountability on him.
uh even when it may not be that, you
know, but he's showing everybody, you
know what, I'm going to keep upping in
my Annie and um it just never it never
sways and that's what that's what makes
him the greatest coach in the world, you
know, he's he's non-stop always there
fearlessly uh in front of everyone uh
show leading the way and and showing
them how how it's done the right way
with integrity and um that's why we love
him, man.
>> Thanks for having us.
>> Have a good one, guys. Merry Christmas.
>> Merry Christmas.
Bo Nicks who's in the pocket being
chased. He pivots away as on the chase
is Amen. And the throw down the field is
incomplete AND MAYBE INTERCEPTED. IT'S
INTERCEPTED BY NICK BOLTON OFF THE
DEFLECTION. THE DEFLECTION BY FULTON. HE
KNOCKED IT INTO THE ARMS OF A DIVING
NICK BOLTON. THE CHIEFS GET A TURNOVER
IN DENVER TERRITORY.
It's awesome that we get to talk to this
guy on our Chiefs Rewind because he has
been an absolute stalwart, especially in
the last five weeks. What about the
effort in this game, not just from the
defense, but offense and special teams
to have a shot at winning this game?
>> Yeah, we came out here, we just wanted
to uh present an attitude, man. Uh last
game, I don't think we played our best
as a team, especially on defense, as a
unit. And uh when we go out there, put
good stuff on tape, man. Play around
with the guys. We said that at the
beginning of this week, man. year from
year to year things change, people
change. Just especially our linebacker
room especially that stuff changes year
to year. So just want to take advantage
of every moment you got with the guys
and just don't leave nothing out the
chance. Leave anything a what if or
leave out [crying] the chance. So super
competitive guys from snap one to the
end, man. Just putting putting the
hearts on the line give a chance to win
the football game at the end.
>> Middle of this defense, Nick Bolt and uh
you guys it looked like you were playing
physical tonight. Many times I said the
guy's head got turned. How about you
guys coming in to be physical tonight in
this game?
>> Yeah, we had a lot of guys um out head
into the week. So, uh, push on the point
position, man. I give those guys a lot
of pride cuz they run the ball on the
edges, man. No whims, rocking screens,
getting off blocks, setting, resetting
the line of scrimmage, rocking screens,
running backs, all that type of stuff.
So, super super proud of those guys, the
young guys, especially hopping in there,
playing a lot of guys playing around
today. And, uh, yeah, seeing them going
out to execute the game plan on a short
week. I was super proud of that as well.
But, yeah, the energy and effort, man,
it was there. The crowd was jumping.
We're just feeling out the energy that
they had today.
>> We were talking on the Cheese Kingdom
show. So close to interceptions. You got
one.
>> Yeah, got one.
What happened on that play?
>> Yeah, man. Uh, just kind of got a
scramble play. I had the back and man
coverage. Um, Christian Fortune went
straight into the ball. Got a PPU ball.
Got patted up. Right place, right time,
man. Had to get a t for our team. We
talked all week about getting offensive
short field and we're able to do that on
our drive.
>> Double digit tackles again. The 23rd
time in your career. Only Derek Johnson
has more and you're closing in on him.
>> What about staying on it, staying tough,
staying keeping everybody alive, and
every snap you're playing like it's the
playoffs.
>> Yeah, man. Uh just kind of mindset kind
of playing a mic backer, playing
linebacker in general. I just got to
have the mindset. It doesn't matter what
the circumstances are, man. You're going
to be who you are or be who you say you
are. And it's kind of just my mindset
week in week out. I just try to be who I
say I am. And um the guys on me to make
sure I'm I'm I'm who I say I am. And the
coaches do as well. Uh fans, teammates,
everything. So So yeah, man. Every
weekend, week out, I try to be
consistent with the work and preparation
and give myself a chance to go out there
and just execute at a high level.
>> Absolute rock solid Nick Bull.
Chris on that that fourth down.
>> I know, man. I know. I'm beating myself
up.
I know. I know. I know. Um
yeah, that could have saved us four
points. Um I felt like the guard moved.
Um but yeah, I critical situation. I got
to be better. H I'm going beat myself up
about that one. Uh so close.
I know it, man. I know it. I know it. I
mean, we're we're right there.
>> Does it feel symptomatic of this season?
I mean, there's been it feels like you
guys have kind of been snake bit in
those close and late situations and and
you know, whether it's, you know, miss
field goal or whatever it is, it seems
like you guys just the coin flip comes
the wrong way this year.
>> We've been beating oursel up this year a
lot, especially with like critical
errors and critical situations. It's
like
I can't do that, man.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I can't do that. Um, but yeah,
this been happening over the year.
We'll get better.
>> How ready are you to watch the season
away and you focus on just that
offseason process and getting better?
>> Listen, man, we got like one more game
left. It's like we got to focus on the
now. You got to be where your feet at.
You got to be present. Um, and you still
got areas you can get better in to close
the season. You know what I mean? And
then we got a lot of young guys playing
um who is broadcasting their talent. So
I don't think you can look at offseason
now when the season is over with. Then
you can analyze your play then look at
areas you can get better in
>> this game meant nothing but it looked
like the player you Nick Pton all the
guys have like a lot of energy. I guess
where do you think that that stem from?
>> This game meant something to us. I mean
we're out there playing. Um still
another opportunity to play the play the
game we love. you know, um it's
unfortunate that we're not fighting for
playoff positioning right now. Uh but
we'll be back. We'll be back. This year
taught us a lot of valuable lessons as
as a team and we're going to continue to
build off of that.
>> I wanted to ask you about one of the old
guys, too. Um you know, there's a lot of
focus outside the building on Travis's
future and whether this might have been
his last game here. Is that something
you as one of his teammates have given
any thought to that 87 might have run in
that tunnel for the last time?
>> I hope not, man. Damn. I mean, dang.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. We just have been
through so much together, man. And
Travis has been a pivotal point of this
offense for so long. And you know, it's
been like a brother, man. It's like to
watch Trav go. I hope this isn't the
last year. I hope he give it one more
year. Just one more, man. Just one more.
Chris, what does he mean just to the
identity of your team and just the
characteristics that you guys want to
display week in week out?
>> I think we we play hard first and
foremost. Um, we play fast and we play
physical. Uh, I mean those three traits
right there win you a lot of football
games.
>> Chris, it looked like you were the first
one he met when he walked through the
tunnel. He kind of waited on him. Why
was that moment important to
>> Um, I think we just walked through the
tunnel together. You know what I mean?
We just walk through the tunnel
together, talk about the game, you know,
dap each other up.
>> What did you see on the third down sack?
That was a huge play in that draft.
>> Steve Spanoya called a great play.
>> Set [snorts] us up, put us in a position
to to to execute. We was running caged
in, so we was able to bring him down. He
got out of the pocket a lot today. We
got to watch film. We got to tighten up
the the screws on the defensive line,
but
we left some opportunities out there.
>> They had so many long drives, not only
number of plays, but length of time. How
much did that wear on you guys late in
the game, you know, because I think they
had nine 47 47 second drive, two other
eight minute drives. I mean, how much
does that wear you guys down?
>> I think we were conditioned for it. Uh,
not too many players was exhausted. I
mean, we was doing a great job of
subbing in and subbing out, getting new
bodies on the field, um, especially in
critical situations. So, I don't think
fatigue played a part in the game.
>> Thank you, Chris.
>> Thank you, guys. Merry Christmas.
>> Chiefs lose 20 to 13 to the Denver
Broncos, but again, theme of this show
is the effort this team gave tonight.
had a chance to win with a lineup that
had like nine starters on injured
reserve including four more that would
put on actually five more with Niko Rio
yesterday. Okay. Defensively in this
game, Null Williams, very exciting. Uh
the way he played physically, if you're
going to play press, man, he he is an
excellent uh press, cover, corner.
>> Yeah, this is one of those blessings in
disguise where we're down our top two
corners, but that means null has to go
out there and play virtually every snap.
And we saw a lot from Null tonight. Uh
he had a lot of good tape here tonight,
I think, both uh in the passing game
deep down the field with sticky
coverage, but also as a run defender,
and we knew that about Null coming out
of Cal that he was a good run defender,
fearless, not afraid to make tackles and
numerous times in the game here tonight.
Made tackles from behind the line of
scrimmage. Really encouraging stuff from
N Williams for sure.
>> We talked about um not giving up, but
just one sack on offense. On defense,
the Chiefs got a sack. Why is that a big
deal? Denver's the best team in the
league at preventing sacks and Chris
Jones got a sack, but it hasn't happened
very often to Bo Knicks.
>> Yeah, that was a big play and a big
moment on third down. Gave us a chance
to tie the game, I believe. Uh, but
think about player development again.
All the guys that got into this game.
Uh, Cooper McDonald was playing a lot of
defense here in this game. Cooper
McDonald was a tryyout player that
earned a spot on this team way back in
the summer, played some defense for us
tonight. Zack Pickkins, who's been kind
of biting his time on the practice
squad, played 17 games a couple years
ago uh for somebody else, but a young
developmental player played some
football for us tonight. And Jeffrey
Bosa was out there as a coverage
linebacker several times here tonight.
So, I'm fired up. And how about
Christian Fulton? Christian Fulton got
out there and uh you know, we gave
Christian a big contract in the
offseason, but he was injured coming
into the year, was kind of behind the
the playbook because he didn't have a
chance to get out there in training camp
much. But Christian Fulton showed us
tonight why he got a big contract in the
offseason and I'm looking forward to
seeing what he can do now in the
offseason training program when healthy
and next year for us because he played
some really good football for us
tonight.
>> And a takeaway he got the pass
deflected. Nick Bolton gets the
interception and uh a take the Chiefs
only 12 takeaways this year. Only two
team and then giving up the third down
and 10 for 17 on the last drive. Their
their go-ahead drive. Oh, it's a killer.
You get them off the field at that point
it gets interesting.
>> Yeah, it does. We still made them sweat
tonight though. And thinking about this
team and their resolve, you know, we
talked on Field Pass about how our guys,
even though it wasn't pretty last week,
they still fought. They still wanted to
win that game. Well, tonight, yeah, we
lost. But, you know, with the
circumstances we've dealt with this
year, knowing we're not going to the
postseason and having all these players
injured, our guys fought and they made
the Broncos who have a chance at the one
seed this year sweat in the end. And,
uh, that's certainly a good indicator
for next season if you ask me. And if
this was Travis Kelce's last home game,
it was only fitting that he gave effort
on the final uh target to him with two
guys all over him to dive for the ball
like it was the first play of his
career. Chiefs lose it, but a lot of
encouraging signs. Enjoy your long
weekend. Now, the Chiefs will close out
the season next week against the Raiders
on the road.
Chief Rewind is brought to you by Ford,
[music] the official car and truck of
the Kansas City Chiefs, and by Community
America Credit Union, the official
banking partner of the Kansas City
Chiefs.